Guide to the Medical Center Public Relations records, 1913-1999 RG0045
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Medical School faculty, 1950-1989; RG0045 Series 9; 1 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  - Charles S. White [3/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 29.7)
  - Charles S. White [4/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 29.8)
  - Charles S. White [5/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 29.9)
  - Charles S. White [6/6], undated (Box 1, Folder 29.1)
  - Negative - Dr. John Hamilt & Frank Kacca, 03/1951 (Box 1, Folder 29.11)
  - Negative - Dr. Roger Choesuer, Russell McNitt and Charles Stanley White, undated (Box 1, Folder 29.12)
  - Dr. Charles S. White, 02/1963 (Box 1, Folder 29.13)
  - Dr. Charles S. White, undated (Box 1, Folder 29.14)
  - Negative - Dr. Charles S. White, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 29.15)
  - Dr. Charles S. White, undated (Box 1, Folder 29.16)
  - Dr. Charles S. White, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 29.17)
  - Dr. Charles S. White [1/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 29.18)
  - Dr. Charles S. White [2/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 29.19)
  - Dr. Charles S. White [3/3], undated (Box 1, Folder 29.2)
  - Charles S. Wise [1/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 30.1)
  - Charles S. Wise [2/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 30.2)
  - Charles S. Wise [3/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 30.3)
  - Charles S. Wise [4/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 30.4)
  - Charles S. Wise [5/5], undated (Box 1, Folder 30.5)
  - Alvin Wyman [1/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 31.1)
  - Alvin Wyman [2/2], undated (Box 1, Folder 31.2)
  - James Breen, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
    5 copies
  - Lynn George, undated (Box 2, Folder 33.1)
  - Jon Clarich talking with Lynn H. George, undated (Box 2, Folder 33.2)
  - Sally Brewster Jamieson, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    Photo and neg; 5 copies
  - Burnice H. Jarman, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    3 copies
  - Ronald P. Kaufman, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    Photo and neg; 7 copies
  - J.H. Lewis, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - James S. Parker, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Neel Price, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Mike Ryan, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    2 copies
  - James C. Walsh, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Photographs and negatives, 1948-1981; RG0045 Series 10; 2 Linear feet (Box 4, Box 3, Box 2, Box 1)
  This series contains photographs and negatives. Subjects in this series include Alpha Omega Alpha, Beaumont Society, Brian Blades, convocations, commencements, emergency room, faculty, John Parks, medical buildings, St. Mary's Court, and campus scenes. The materials date from 1948-81.
  - Acupuncture Model, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    photos
  - Administrators, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alpha Omega Alpha, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    photos, negatives, lecture announcement
  - Alumni, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    photos and news clippings
  - Alumni Council, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Council, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Events, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    photos of banquet, weekend and Dean's breakfast
  - Anatomy building/classroom, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    photos (includes classes from early 1900's)
  - Anesthesiology, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - AMC 79th Annual Meeting, Houston, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    photos and news clipping
  - ARCS Tour, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    photos and negatives
  - Awards to students, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Awards Tea, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Beaumont Society, 1966-1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    photos, negatives and news clippings
  - Bessis, Marcel, hemotology, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Blades, Brian, MD, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Blades, Brian 'Statesman in Medicine', 1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Blades, Brian in surgery, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Blubber Club (golf), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Briggs Twins, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    photos and correspondence
  - Budget Office, staff, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Buildings, historical, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Cancer Clinic, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Cardiology Conference: Exercise Airlie House, Spring, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Cardiology Conference, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Chemotherapy, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cheng's visit to China, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Child Health and Development, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Children's Hospital, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    photos and negatives (includes negatives without photos)
  - Chinese delegation to GWUH, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Classroom, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Convocation, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Commencement, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Convocation, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    photo
  - Commencement, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Convocation, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Commencement, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Convocation, Mid-Winter, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    photos and press release
  - Commencement, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Commencement, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Commencement, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Commencement, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    negatives
  - Commencement, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Commencement, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Commencement and President's Tea, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Commencement and President's Tea, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - DC Medical Society Luncheons, 1964-1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - DC Medical Society Scholarships, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Department Heads, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Dialysis, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Drug metabolism Workshop, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Duggins, Virginia W., MS Society, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Duncan, Harry F., undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    photos, negatives, news clippings, correspondence
  - Egg fossil with fetal skeleton, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Elliott, Pres., undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    photos at various functions
  - Emergency Room, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    photos including building construction, negatives, press release regarding opening
  - Emergency Room, dedication, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
    photos, negatives, press release
  - Equipment, Hospital, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ethridge Portrait Presentation, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Events: awards, banquets etc., undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Everglades Apartment building, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Photos and negatives; formerly Nurse's dormitory, now JKBO Hall.
  - Faculty, 1960-1970 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    photos with detailed captions and identifications
  - Faculty, 1960-1970 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - GWU Clinic, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    detailed captions and identifications
  - GWU Hospital Art Renderings, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - GWU Medicine Magazine, anniversary issue, art work, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hospital, undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    photos, miscellaneous
  - Medical School, undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    photos, negatives, press releases
  - Negatives, various, undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Nurses, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    group photos
  - Parks, Dr. John, 1960-1969 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Peery, Dr. Thomas, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Portraits, miscellaneous doctors (Kellog lecturers?), 1948 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Registration, students, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Shrine Reception, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Armaly, Dr., undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Negatives (35 mm and 4x5")
  - Awards Ceremonies, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Biochemistry Lab, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Breast Implant, silicon gel, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Buildings, medical, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Children and babies, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Comical slides of medical staff, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Computers, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Davies, Dr. David D., 06/1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Elegart, Dr., dermatology, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Graduation, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Health fairs, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Inspectors, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Library, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - "Matching Day", 1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, hospital, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Mother Teresa, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Nursing, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - People: doctors, staff, patients, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - People: doctors, staff, patients, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Procedures: surgery, etc., undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Quintuplets, Pisner, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Receptions/banquets, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Rehabilitation, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Seminars/conferences, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - St. Mary's Court, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Stage performances, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Television shooting of "Health File", undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Articles, RG0045 Series 11; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains articles. These five bound articles are about the subject of cloning.
  - Articles, clippings and photocopies of articles on cloning, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    In multiple languages. 5 copies
- Graduating class, 1929; RG0045 Series 12; 0.25 Linear feet (Map-folder 1)
  This series contains photographs. This material is from 1929. One images is the The George Washington University Medical School graduating class and another photographs is an individual image of Jean Macfarland Loar (class of 1929)
  Evelyn Rakow, Mrs. Loar's niece donated this collection.
- Slides, RG0045 Series 13; 0.25 Linear feet
  This series contains slides. These 128 slides document the history of the medical school. Topics include the Civil War, students, buildings, John Parks, and President Ronald Reagan.
- Departmental files, 1947-1999; RG0045 Series 14; 8 Linear feet (Box 6, Box 5, Box 7, Box 4, Box 3, Box 2, Box 1)
  This series contains pamphlets, manuals, publications, correspondence, convocations, student handbook, alumni council, meeting minutes, by-laws, constitution, photographs, slides, plaques, and books. This material dates form 1947-99. Subjects of this materials include Governing Board, Medical Society, Medical Alumni Association, alumni reunion weekends, commencements, oration by Fred Gibbs, Ross Hall and buildings on H Street, the Health Sciences chartering ceremony, the statue of George Washington on Washington Circle, Women's Board.
  - 1st annual GW Public Health Programs Recognition Ceremony, 06/23/1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Applications/Programs/Pamphlets on Health Sciences programs, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Articles and newsclips on medicine and doctors, 1965-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Center to Improve the Care of the Dying, 1st and 3rd annual activities report, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Commencement programs - School of Medicine and Health Sciences, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Directories, medical faculty and class of 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Doctoral programs in Biomedical Sciences, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Draft of Strategic plan on the institute of Biomedical Sciences, 12/12/1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Frank N. Miller - Pathology prize, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - GW Management forum - series of presentations, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - GW Research and Human Values, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - GWU-"Campaign Chronicle", 07/1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - GWU-"Consult", 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - GWU-"F.A.N. Mail" Financial Aid Newsletter, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - GWU-"Foggy Bottomline", 02/1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - GWU-"Health Sciences Update", 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - GWU-"Heritage Society" Newsletter, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - GWU-"Informer", 05/01/1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - GWU-"Notes" Fall, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - GWU-"PA News and Views", 02/1999 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - GWU-"Reform Watch", 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - GWUMC International programs, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - GWUMC-"Research Forecast", 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - History of GWs medical center and buildings, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Internship Manual - Department of Health Services Management and Policy, 08/1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Medical Center Hospital - hospital facility development plan, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Medical Center Information, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Medical Center-center for health policy and research, 04/1997 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Medical Center-convocation poster, 09/24/1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Medical Center-Grand Rounds Lectures frontiers in biomedicine, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Medical Center-health sciences research day, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Medical Center-invitations and letters, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Medical school convocation script and invitation, 04/1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Medical student directories, 1990-1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Office of Graduate Medical Education - resident manuals, 07/1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Pamphlets on Public Health programs, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Pamphlets/letters - Medical alumni annual funds and support, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Papers from GWU medical center, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - School of Medicine and Health Sciences Admissions handbook, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - School of Public Health and Health Services - Council on Education for Public Health, 09/1998 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Student handbook for medical students (class of 2000), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Tom Chapman - CEO of GW Medical Center, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Universal Health Services, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Various programs on medical care, research, programming at GW medical center, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Womens Health Center, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Alumni dues and card, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Alumni labels request form, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Alumni leadership Organization, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Relations Committee, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Alumni relations council, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Relations Office-miscellaneous correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Service Awards General Alumni Association, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - General Alumni Association Alumni Community Service Award, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board minutes, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board Meeting, 03/16/1988 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board meeting, 10/19/1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board meeting, 01/18/1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board meeting, 05/1989 --09/1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board meeting, 10/18/1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board meeting, 03/15/1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board meeting, 03/14/1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board meeting, 05/16/1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board meeting, 05/23/1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board meeting, 06/27/1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board meeting, 10/10/1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board meeting, 01/23/1991 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - General Alumni Association Governing Board minutes, 10/17/1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - General Alumni Association, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Medical Alumni Association Alumni Service Award, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Medical Alumni Association Student Achievement Award, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - University Board of Trustees Alumni Trustee nominations, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Alumni Reunion Reception, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend prior to 1975, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend Schedule, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 09/14/1990 --09/15/1990 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Registration slips and scientific session cards, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Certificate from Medical Alumni Association to Hector J. Hidalgo, 05/06/1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Class Parties Reunion Weekend, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Class Reunion Parties, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - CME Registration Reunion, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Fall Alumni Holiday, 11/04/1989 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Future Class Party Hosts for Reunion Weekend, undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Leads for future Reunion Weekend Committees, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Medical Alumni Office - correspondence, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Medical Alumni Reunion Weekend and Fall Holiday, 1989-1996 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Medical Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Pre-1940 Alumni Reunion, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Reunion Status responses, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Council Minutes, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Council, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - By Laws-Constitution, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Committees, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Committees, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Committees-Medical Center, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Council Meeting Minutes, 04/08/1992 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Council Members, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Council Minutes, 1960-1964 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Council Minutes, 1965-1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Council Minutes, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Council Minutes, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Council Minutes, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Council Minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Council Minutes, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Council Minutes, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Finance Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - GWU Medical Society Activities, 1953-1961 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - GWU Medical Society Activities, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - GWU Medical Society and Association Minutes, 1959-1961 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - GWU Medical Society Minutes, 1947-1949 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - GWU Medical Society Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - GWU Medical Society Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - GWU Medical Society Minutes, 1950-1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - GWU Medical Society Minutes, 1953-1956 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - GWU Medical Society, prior to 1947, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Hospitality Committee, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Intermountain Region, 1967-1975 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Medical Alumni Council Curriculum Vitae, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence Alumni Council, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous meetings, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Nominating Committee, 1965-1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Nominating Committee, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Regional Groups, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Smith-Reed-Russell Society, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Stephen S. Pappas, M.D. Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Student Sponsor Program, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Student Sponsor Program, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - AHA annual meeting, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Awards Event, 02/1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Contact prints
  - Alumni Donor Luncheon prior to Convocation, 04/03/1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Photos, "GW Medicine" Magazine
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1995 ca. (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Photos, negatives, contact prints
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Barbecue-Class of 1948, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Class of 1947 and young classes reception, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Convocation Class of 1948, 09/11/1998 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Convocation, Class of 1948, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Cosmos Club Reception Class of 1948, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Dinner, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Evening Classes of 1962, 1967, and 1952, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Friday morning, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Glen Walker lecture, Class of 1948, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Kennedy Center Reception Class of 1948, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Luncheon 1997 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    Photos and pamphlet
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend Mentor/Student breakfast, 10/1996 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Program, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Reception, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend (Saturday), 10/1996 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Seminars Class of 1948, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Alumni Reunion Weekend-Weingold Reception, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    Photos, contact prints
  - Alumni "Summit" meeting, 1995 ca. (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Blades Lecture and Reception, 10/13/1998 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    Photos and contact prints
  - Casino Night, 10/1996 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Ceremony-Awarding Degrees (informal), 1990 ca. (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Commencement, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    Photos, negatives
  - Convocation, 09/11/1998 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - D.C. Med Society, 08/1996 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Donahoe Lecture, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Evelyn Y. Davis Foundation, 1995 ca. (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Fred Gibbs Oration, 04/04/1997 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    Contact prints and program
  - Gibbs Oration, 10/15/1998 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Health Sciences and Hooding Event, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Leadership Luncheon, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Mandel Dinner, 10/1996 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Match Day, 03/ 1995 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Medical Malpractice Colloquium, 10/15/1998 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Miscellaneous photos, 1990 ca. --1998 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Miscellaneous photos-Dean L. Thompson Bowles, 1990 ca. (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Miscellaneous photos-Frank Miller, 1970, 1995 ca. (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Miscellaneous photos-George Washington Bust on GW campus, 1990 ca. (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Miscellaneous photos-Medical School Follies, 1965 ca. (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Miscellaneous photos-Ross Hall and H Street Buildings, 1965 ca. --1990 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Miscellaneous photos-staff, students, 1959-1990 -- --ca. (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Miscellaneous Reception, 1995 ca. (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Miscellaneous Reception, 1995 ca. (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Photos from summer 1992 magazine "GW Magazine" (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Reception for Frank Miller, 04/23/1996 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Residents receiving jackets, 1995 ca. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Ross Hall, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)